{"id":211,"text":"The Securities and Exchange Commission of Nigeria launched a new fintech regulatory framework in Abuja on Friday.","label":[[4,49,"GOVERNMENT_AGENCY"],[97,102,"LOCATION"],[106,112,"DATE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":212,"text":"Aliko Dangote announced plans to expand the Dangote Sugar Refinery with an investment of ₦200 billion.","label":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[44,66,"ORGANISATION"],[89,101,"MONEY"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":213,"text":"The Nigerian Air Force commissioned eight new trainer aircraft at the Kaduna Air Base yesterday.","label":[[4,22,"GOVERNMENT_AGENCY"],[70,85,"LOCATION"],[86,95,"DATE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":214,"text":"Access Bank Plc announced a ₦50 billion credit facility for small and medium-sized enterprises in Abuja.","label":[[0,15,"ORGANISATION"],[27,39,"MONEY"],[98,103,"LOCATION"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":215,"text":"The Nigerian National Petroleum Company Limited signed a joint venture agreement with TotalEnergies.","label":[[4,47,"GOVERNMENT_AGENCY"],[86,99,"ORGANISATION"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":216,"text":"Dr. Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala met with the Minister of Finance in Abuja to discuss trade policy reforms.","label":[[0,23,"PERSON"],[60,65,"LOCATION"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":218,"text":"Zenith Bank reported a profit after tax of ₦405 billion for the 2025 financial year.","label":[[0,20,"ORGANISATION"],[43,55,"MONEY"],[63,68,"DATE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":219,"text":"Governor Babajide Sanwo-Olu launched a new housing scheme worth ₦30 billion in Ikorodu.","label":[[9,27,"PERSON"],[64,75,"MONEY"],[79,86,"LOCATION"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":220,"text":"The Economic and Financial Crimes Commission arrested three contractors in Port Harcourt over alleged fraud.","label":[[4,44,"GOVERNMENT_AGENCY"],[75,88,"LOCATION"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":221,"text":"MTN Nigeria announced plans to roll out 5G services to Benin and Warri before December.","label":[[0,11,"ORGANISATION"],[55,60,"LOCATION"],[65,70,"LOCATION"],[78,86,"DATE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":222,"text":"The House of Representatives passed the Petroleum Industry Amendment Bill on Wednesday.","label":[[4,28,"GOVERNMENT_AGENCY"],[77,86,"DATE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":223,"text":"Airtel Africa recorded revenue growth of 8 per cent in the first quarter of 2026.","label":[[0,13,"ORGANISATION"],[41,51,"PERCENTAGE"],[59,80,"DATE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":224,"text":"The Federal Executive Council approved ₦120 billion for road rehabilitation across the six geo-political zones.","label":[[4,29,"GOVERNMENT_AGENCY"],[39,51,"MONEY"],[87,110,"LOCATION"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":225,"text":"Fidelity Bank donated ₦200 million to support flood victims in Bayelsa State.","label":[[0,13,"ORGANISATION"],[22,34,"MONEY"],[63,76,"LOCATION"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":226,"text":"Minister of Education Tahir Mamman announced the construction of ten new technical colleges nationwide.","label":[[22,34,"PERSON"],[92,102,"LOCATION"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":227,"text":"The Nigerian Stock Exchange recorded a daily trade volume of ₦6.3 billion on Thursday.","label":[[4,27,"GOVERNMENT_AGENCY"],[61,73,"MONEY"],[77,85,"DATE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":228,"text":"Flour Mills of Nigeria commissioned a new pasta plant in Kwara State valued at ₦75 billion.","label":[[0,22,"ORGANISATION"],[57,68,"LOCATION"],[79,90,"MONEY"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":229,"text":"The Lagos State Police Command deployed officers to Ikoyi following a security alert on Friday morning.","label":[[4,30,"GOVERNMENT_AGENCY"],[52,58,"LOCATION"],[88,95,"DATE"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":230,"text":"The World Bank approved a $500 million loan to improve power distribution in Nigeria’s northern region.","label":[[4,14,"ORGANISATION"],[26,38,"MONEY"],[77,102,"LOCATION"]],"Comments":[]}
